Guide to the Peter Beste and Lance Scott Walker Houston Rap Collection
University of Houston Libraries
- Music and Video
  - 45 rpm records
    - DJ Screw/Fat Pat 7″ record included in Houston Rap deluxe bundle, 6 copies (Box 6, Item 13-18)